<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Smriti&#39;s webpage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:61907/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Smriti&#39;s webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:61907/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My lessons from gaming</title>
      <link>http://localhost:61907/post/2025/05/07/my-lessons-from-gaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:61907/post/2025/05/07/my-lessons-from-gaming/</guid>
      <description>For anyone who knows me, my absolute lack of hand-eye coordination is pretty obvious. A scooter ride gone bad in high school, left me with a half functioning elbow and two neourologically numb fingers on my left hand.&#xA;One of the biggest reason that I&amp;rsquo;m a strictly computational scientist is my extremely shaky hands and general propensity to drop things. I think the most challenging course for me was my second year Optics lab course at IITK.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My first blogpost: This time for sure</title>
      <link>http://localhost:61907/post/2025/02/02/my-first-blogpost-this-time-for-sure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:61907/post/2025/02/02/my-first-blogpost-this-time-for-sure/</guid>
      <description>I have a confession to make. This website has been in the development stage for more than a year. I have had a layout ready this whole time. I figured out how to make Hugo work to my liking for months. But the &amp;ldquo;rate determining step&amp;rdquo; has been my apprehension to write that first post.&#xA;I have never written a blog post, countless dear diary entries sure but I haven&amp;rsquo;t ever put my partially cooked thoughts out on the internet before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:61907/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:61907/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Smriti Pradhan, a PhD candidate in Physics at Brandeis University working with Prof. Michael.F.Hagan. My research primarily focuses on using coarse-grained simulation techniques to understand the assembly of Hepatits B Virus and how it&amp;rsquo;s impeded in the presence of Core-protein Allosteric Modulators (CpAMs).&#xA;I did my undergrad and masters in Physics at Indian Institute of Technology, Kanpur. For my master&amp;rsquo;s thesis research I worked with Prof. Debashish Chowdhury to understand the stochastic process of decision-making and traffic management in ant colonies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outreach and teaching</title>
      <link>http://localhost:61907/outreach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:61907/outreach/</guid>
      <description>boop</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research Experiences</title>
      <link>http://localhost:61907/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:61907/research/</guid>
      <description>List of my most recent projects.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
