<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Smriti Pradhan</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Smriti Pradhan</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why I love markov state models and so should you</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2025/09/17/why-i-love-markov-state-models-and-so-should-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2025/09/17/why-i-love-markov-state-models-and-so-should-you/</guid>
      <description>In this post I&amp;rsquo;ll talk about a tool I have used quite extensively in my research and which is very close to my heart. Over the course of the post we&amp;rsquo;ll go into understanding:&#xA;What is markov property? State of the system at a future time only depends on state of the system currently and not history of the system. This means if we know what the system looks like currently we can predict the state for future time steps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My lessons from gaming</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2025/05/07/my-lessons-from-gaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2025/05/07/my-lessons-from-gaming/</guid>
      <description>For anyone who knows me, my absolute lack of hand-eye coordination is pretty obvious. A scooter ride gone bad in high school, left me with a half functioning elbow and two neourologically numb fingers on my left hand.&#xA;One of the biggest reason that I&amp;rsquo;m a strictly computational scientist is my extremely shaky hands and general propensity to drop things. I think the most challenging course for me was my second year Optics lab course at IITK.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My first blogpost: This time for sure</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2025/02/02/my-first-blogpost-this-time-for-sure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2025/02/02/my-first-blogpost-this-time-for-sure/</guid>
      <description>I have a confession to make. This website has been in the development stage for more than a year. I have had a layout ready this whole time. I figured out how to make Hugo work to my liking for months. But the &amp;ldquo;rate determining step&amp;rdquo; has been my apprehension to write that first post.&#xA;I have never written a blog post, countless dear diary entries sure but I haven&amp;rsquo;t ever put my partially cooked thoughts out on the internet before.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
